<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News on RPI Crows</title><link>http://www.rpicrows.com/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on RPI Crows</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 21:21:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.rpicrows.com/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>COVID Relief Fundraiser Every Donation Counts!</title><link>http://www.rpicrows.com/news/covid-relief-fundraiser-update-2022-08-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 21:21:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.rpicrows.com/news/covid-relief-fundraiser-update-2022-08-10/</guid><description>&lt;p>We again would like to thank you for your recent donations to our COVID-19 Relief Fundraiser. We have made great progress towards our fundraising efforts thanks to the generous donations of 39 brothers.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Every donation, no matter the size, will make a difference. We still need your help to reach our goal of $90K which will reposition our Chapter back to our pre-pandemic financial levels so we can tackle much needed maintenance work on our properties, reinforce our recruitment efforts to attract a new generation of Brothers, and strengthen our scholarship funds to provide support for our undergraduate Brothers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>COVID Relief Fundraiser Update</title><link>http://www.rpicrows.com/news/covid-relief-fundraiser-update-2022-06-28/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 17:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.rpicrows.com/news/covid-relief-fundraiser-update-2022-06-28/</guid><description>&lt;p>We wanted to personally thank you for your recent donations to our COVID-19 Relief Fundraiser. We are happy to announce that with the generous donations that we have received thus far over these past few weeks we have already met our first goal of raising over $36K! These funds will provide much needed support to our Chapter as we recover from this crisis, and we are well on our way of ensuring that Alpha Chi Rho will always be there for our alumni Brothers, our current undergraduate Brothers, and our future Brothers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>COVID Relief Fundraiser</title><link>http://www.rpicrows.com/news/covid-relief-fundraiser-2022-06-16/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 17:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.rpicrows.com/news/covid-relief-fundraiser-2022-06-16/</guid><description>&lt;p>The COVID-19 Pandemic has caused a major adverse effect on the livelihood of our Chapter at RPI over the past two years. Membership numbers have been dwindling due to increased difficulties in recruitment during the pandemic. Both the pandemic and RPI’s policies have reduced the number of Brothers currently living in our Houses creating significant detrimental consequences on both the fraternal and financial aspects of our Chapter.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>During the initial stages of the pandemic in Spring 2020, all students were sent home and thus the Building Association was unable to collect rent. Furthermore, the following year, Fall 2020-Spring 2021, RPI adopted online classes, so most of the undergraduate Brothers did not return to the Chapter, and again minimal rent was collected. Further exacerbating the lack of income, recruitment efforts over these semesters were very difficult and more Brothers graduated than have been newly initiated. The Building Association has taken a massive loss in finances over these past two years as we continue to pay for our required expenses and receive minimal income through rent.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Spring 2022 Building Association Meeting</title><link>http://www.rpicrows.com/news/spring-2022-ba-meeting-wrapup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 17:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.rpicrows.com/news/spring-2022-ba-meeting-wrapup/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Building Association held its semi-annual general meeting fully virtually via Zoom on 4/24/2022, with 23 Brothers in attendance.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Grad Weekend Fall 2021</title><link>http://www.rpicrows.com/news/grad-weekend-fall-21/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 12:12:36 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.rpicrows.com/news/grad-weekend-fall-21/</guid><description>&lt;p>The RCAF and Delta Phi of Alpha Chi Rho Building Association successfully hosted the bi-annual Grad Weekend event on November 7, 2021. Events were hosted both virtually and in-person.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The General Meeting was held from 10:30AM-12:30 PM Sunday morning with 25+ members in attendance. The meeting minutes have been uploaded to the Google Drive.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>