<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FAQs on RPI Crows</title><link>http://axpmightymouse.github.io/faqs/</link><description>Recent content in FAQs on RPI Crows</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 16:40:23 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://axpmightymouse.github.io/faqs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Living at the House</title><link>http://axpmightymouse.github.io/faqs/living-at-the-house/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://axpmightymouse.github.io/faqs/living-at-the-house/</guid><description>Responsibilities Waitings – Many fraternities have cooks that they pay to come to their house and prepare their meals for them. Others have catering services that bring them their meals. At our house, we strive to be self-sufficient so we adhere to a system in which every brother is required to be a “waiter” one day a week. We normally have 4 or 5 people waiting each day dinner is served.</description></item><item><title>Postulancy</title><link>http://axpmightymouse.github.io/faqs/postulancy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://axpmightymouse.github.io/faqs/postulancy/</guid><description>What is Postulancy? New members do not pledge Alpha Chi Rho. Instead, they enter into postulancy,which is a period in which one is an uneducated equal. It takes time for new members to learn the history and ideals of the fraternity. This period will last approximately 8 weeks during which postulants are expected to learn what it means to be a brother. This includes participating in new member education classes, Rensselaer’s Greek Life 101 programming, community service, and other brotherhood events.</description></item><item><title>Why Go Greek?</title><link>http://axpmightymouse.github.io/faqs/why-go-greek/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://axpmightymouse.github.io/faqs/why-go-greek/</guid><description>Friendship and Brotherhood As a member of Alpha Chi Rho, you will form friendships unlike those found in other organizations. Alpha Chi Rho is composed of members with a diverse set of interests from Capoeira to Jazz Ensemble to ROTC. Your brothers will grow to become your closest friends, those who will cheer you on when you’re successful and who will support you when the going gets tough. This unbreakable support system will allow for experiences in many activities that you wouldn’t attempt on your own.</description></item></channel></rss>