<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on RPI Crows</title><link>http://www.rpicrows.com/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on RPI Crows</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.rpicrows.com/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Local Chapter History</title><link>http://www.rpicrows.com/about/local-chapter-history/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.rpicrows.com/about/local-chapter-history/</guid><description>&lt;p>Late in the fall semester of 1946, a group of 15 members of the class of 1950 concerned themselves with the rather inevitable fate of separation and absorption by other group on campus. A small committee was appointed to investigate possibilities of organizing a new fraternity with the goal of keeping this group and its ideals intact. It was touch and go for several months while some of the members plunged ahead with the business at hand, others remaining undecided. Finally, when a constitution and working organization were readied, there were 13 men standing by to become members of what was first termed a club. With the election of officers in March of 1947, Phi Delta Rho came into being.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>National History</title><link>http://www.rpicrows.com/about/national-history/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.rpicrows.com/about/national-history/</guid><description>&lt;p>History can be presented in many forms. It can be written or oral. This historical outlook on the trials and triumphs of our Brotherhood was taken from articles which have appeared in the Garnet &amp;amp; White, from personal letters in the Fraternity’s archives, and from personal discussions with Brothers who shared their stories with us.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The year was 1894. Grover Cleveland was the President of the United States. The country was starting to recover from the Economic Panic of 1893, which seriously jeopardized the monetary and fiscal policies of both the country and its individuals.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Our Properties</title><link>http://www.rpicrows.com/about/our-properties/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.rpicrows.com/about/our-properties/</guid><description>&lt;p>Alpha Chi Rho consists of three houses on 4 property lots located between Tibbits Ave. and Highland Ave. We are located approximately two blocks from the main campus, making it an easy walk to and from class. Every room has a Cable TV connection and also a high speed internet port for each brother. The House will supply each room with a desk, bed, and chair, although many brothers choose to provide their own for reasons of comfort. Brothers are also free to modify rooms to suit their needs, whether it be lofting beds, adding futons, or simply repainting. The property is owned by the Delta Phi Building Association and rented to the undergraduate chapter.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>